{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Second Floor Addition Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/62349/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62349,"taskName":"Second Story Addition - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Second Story Addition","xmTaskDescriptor":"Second Floor Addition Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"second story, second floor","textMessagingName":"2nd Story Additn","rolloverLongDesc":"Can be under or on top of the existing structure. These firms are general contractors who specialize in building additions. They supply or coordinate all the relevant services including foundations, framing, plumbing, HVAC, electrical, drywall, flooring, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Add add a second floor to a home.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Second Floor Addition.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Second Story Addition Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Add a Second Floor","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Second Story Addition","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Second Story Addition - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Addition","urlName":"Second-Story-Addition","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Second Story Addition Builders in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Addition, Build, Structure, general, contractor, 2nd, second, story","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8790,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62349/":{"taskOID":62349,"originalTaskOID":62349,"setID":8790,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500766,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":201194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design and build","answerDisplayText":"Design and build","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201196,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503013,"questionDisplayText":"What type of second floor addition will this be?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of second floor addition will this be?","shortQuestionText":"What type of second floor addition will this be?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203912,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Partial Addition","answerDisplayText":"Partial Addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203913,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Full addition","answerDisplayText":"Full addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203914,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition above a garage","answerDisplayText":"Addition above a garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500984,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms Included:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the rooms included in this project:","shortQuestionText":"Select the rooms included in this project:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2728,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Garage/Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Garage/Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3633,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Living/Family room","answerDisplayText":"Living/Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Laundry/Mud room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry/Mud room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1846,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Deck/Porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck/Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200381,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Office(s)","answerDisplayText":"Office(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200380,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Common area(s)","answerDisplayText":"Common area(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160804,"questionDisplayText":"Requires Work on Historical Structure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Does this project require work on a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160805,"questionDisplayText":"Request for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request for a commercial (non-residential) location?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500766,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":201194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design and build","answerDisplayText":"Design and build","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201196,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":201194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design and build","answerDisplayText":"Design and build","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201196,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503013,"questionDisplayText":"What type of second floor addition will this be?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of second floor addition will this be?","shortQuestionText":"What type of second floor addition will this be?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203912,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Partial Addition","answerDisplayText":"Partial Addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203913,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Full addition","answerDisplayText":"Full addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203914,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition above a garage","answerDisplayText":"Addition above a garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203912,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Partial Addition","answerDisplayText":"Partial Addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203913,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Full addition","answerDisplayText":"Full addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203914,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition above a garage","answerDisplayText":"Addition above a garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500984,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms Included:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the rooms included in this project:","shortQuestionText":"Select the rooms included in this project:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2728,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Garage/Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Garage/Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3633,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Living/Family room","answerDisplayText":"Living/Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Laundry/Mud room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry/Mud room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1846,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Deck/Porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck/Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200381,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Office(s)","answerDisplayText":"Office(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200380,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Common area(s)","answerDisplayText":"Common area(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2728,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Garage/Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Garage/Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3633,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Living/Family room","answerDisplayText":"Living/Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Laundry/Mud room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry/Mud room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1846,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Deck/Porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck/Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200381,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Office(s)","answerDisplayText":"Office(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200380,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Common area(s)","answerDisplayText":"Common area(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160804,"questionDisplayText":"Requires Work on Historical Structure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Does this project require work on a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160805,"questionDisplayText":"Request for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request for a commercial (non-residential) location?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}